Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on the cruise.
We are.
What was that?
It's Sorcery!
Oh, he's a freak!
A magical freak!
He sent Captain Kaido fine!
I'll just leave this to you.
I've got treasure to find.
Use our pirates!
Have a ride!
No, don't! Stay away!
Say your prayers, butler! Take that!
And that!
Game over, you lousy,
Newgate pirate! No! Stop it!
Those kids! What are they doing?
Those Rugrats have a death wish.
You don't know what you're doing!
Stop!
All right.
This time we'll let you off
without any more brutality.
This time.
Now those stupid kids have really done it.
Captain Kuro is going to be so mad.
Captain! I knew it!
You were fighting!
Gosh, that is so totally awesome!
I thought there were no
secrets between us pirates.
Why didn't you tell us?
That's right!
We're supposed to tell each other
everything cares about that.
Look, this is important.
You guys got to get out of here run
We have to stand fight
with you do you thought
pirates will be shamed if we run in fear
Captain!
That hurt.
Hmm.
My, my.
That's quite a strange technique
you've developed there.
Tell me something.
Do you have powers from
eating the Devil Fruit?
Yep.
I'm a rubber man.
He ate the Devil Fruit.
That guy's dangerous.
Those Devil Fruit people are real.
He's got rubber arms of death.
It makes perfect sense now.
I didn't just hallucinate his
arm stretching out like that.
Jungle.
Sir.
I can handle the boy.
You take care of Miss
Kaya like we planned.
Have her ride her butler into her will?
Then kill her.
As for the kids, they're an eyesore.
Eliminate them.
I'm on it.
Stop right there.
If you want to get to them, you'll
have to make it through me first.
Huh?
Geek!
Star-sipper!
Not again.
that guy he's crazy oh no kaya
no stay away from
her no don't no
OOSA PIRATES!
Yes, sir!
I need you to listen carefully.
Look, we're not running.
Not after they did this to you.
We will avenge you.
Protect Kaya.
Do as I say.
Don't argue with me.
I'm giving you the most important
task there is right now.
It's absolutely critical that you succeed.
Take Kaya and get away from here.
You must keep her safe.
This is the reason we
wanted to be pirates.
To protect what's dear to us.
So do as I say.
And run!
Usa.
Now go.
That's a direct order. Yes! Captain!
Kaya, hurry! This way! Come on! Let's go!
He sure got away with words.
He made running away sound brave.
I know these words like
the back of my hand.
Okay.
Jungle.
Yeah, sorry, I was gawking.
Those fools, do they really
think that they can escape me?
Gotcha.
Damn you!
He's not a priority right now.
Yes, sir!
Their attempt at escape is futile.
We know all too well how weak Kaeya is.
There is no way they can
possibly escape Jango.
Now, if you want to help her, go ahead.
But first, you'll have to get
off this hill alive, Usopp.
Huh, Bucci!
I guess losing to me once
wasn't enough for you, huh?
I told you to get out of my
way, you fooling tub of a lord!
Now I'm blown!
Aaaah!
Honey, is that weird
hypnotist guy still behind us?
I don't know.
I can't see him anymore.
Let's make sure and lose it for good.
There's no way that nutjob could
catch up to us in our own forest.
Don't you worry, Miss Kaya.
The Oshoff pirates are going
to keep you safe and sound.
That's right.
The Oshoff pirates stand by their word.
Thank you so much.
Well, they're not there.
Bulls, I'm coming to get you!
Do you really think you can run from me?
We could do this the easy way?
or I could just level this entire forest!
Whoa, that guy is really mad.
And he can do a lot more
than just hypnotize people.
Where have you gone?
Wait, what was that sound?
That is the sound of destruction.
Jungo's probably tearing the place apart.
Go ahead.
See for yourself if you can get up.
Heartless bastard,
don't you even have a shred of pity you
lived with that girl for three years?
No, I've told you Kaya is nothing
more than a pawn in the game.
I intend to win when she's dead
then I'll be grateful to her.
Damn you.
This guy is hopelessly evil.
We should put him out of his misery.
Hey!
Usa!
Go find the others!
Don't worry.
We'll take care of this guy.
Go on.
Ah very impressive you can still move.
Shut up!
You won't get away with this!
I won't let you.
You betrayed the villagers'
trust not to mention
you plan to take the life
of a sweet young girl.
No!
This is the last time
you ever get your way!
Usopp!
It hurts.
It hurts so bad.
I can't move.
You really are a riot.
Just stay on the ground there.
Even if you did somehow catch up to Jango,
he'd end your life in the blink of an eye.
Staying there is what's best for you.
I don't care.
Hm?
I don't care that I'm weak.
I'll protect them.
I'm captain of the Usopp Pirates.
A brave warrior of the sea who
fights for what he holds dear.
I will protect everyone in
the village if it kills me.
On my word, you will never
set foot in that village!
What's his deal?
He's yelling about something.
Check it out, he's crying.
What's so funny?
Luffy, me and Usopp are going
to chase down that hypno-freak.
Is that a problem? No. Hurry!
Hey, thank you.
I'd be a whole lot faster
if I was going by myself.
But I don't know those woods.
So if we're going to catch up to
them, I'm going to need your help.
Hold it, you two.
Where do you think you're going?
Who gave you permission
to go anywhere? I did!
Miss, Zoro, get going!
Have another!
Gums!
Man, he disappeared again!
The others got away.
That's the most important thing, really.
Before I kill you, I
feel compelled to ask.
What is an outsider like you budding
into this village's business for?
Because there's a man in this
village that I don't want to let die.
Simple enough are you okay with
that being the reason that you die?
Sure am.
But I'm not gonna die.
We'll see about that.
This is quite boring.
You cocky jerk.
Go east.
Hey, I said go east, so go east already.
This is the wrong direction.
Fine, east.
Is that left or right? Turn right.
But that's where we came from.
Ms. Kaya!
I'm sorry.
You should go on without me.
What are you talking about?
We're under strict orders to protect you.
Oh, no.
She's got a really bad fever.
What?
Hang in there, Kaya. A doctor.
We need a doctor.
You idiot.
We don't have time for that.
Someone's trying to kill her.
But it's dangerous for her to run anymore.
Yeah, but...
Show yourselves, you ruts.
Thank you for helping me.
Just the thought is more than enough.
Now go, all of you.
Where did you brats go?
If we left Kaya and ran away right
now, we would probably survive, right?
Yeah, probably.
And our captain always
said to run with your tail
between your legs if you
think you're gonna lose?
Then again our captain is a liar!
But even he didn't take
his own advice he tried
so hard to protect us he
risked his life for us!
Swore to protect Kyle.
All right, then prepare
yourselves to stop pirates.
We gotta fight him.
Let's do it Stop this!
You're no match for him!
You're only kids!
You mustn't put your life
on the line for my sake!
If we don't want to die, we
have to fight for our lives!
Oh...
He nicked me!
Kuro laid him out flat!
Lot of good that Devil Fruit did him!
Yeah, that's Captain Kuro for ya!
Shut up!
Don't call me that!
You still don't get it.
You fools.
This whole plan was devised so that I
may be rid of that name once and for all.
I'm tired of it.
Concocting plans every day for a bunch of
barbarians who care only
about havoc and mayhem.
Relentlessly attacked by
government dogs and bounty hunters.
I'm tired of it.
I am sick and tired of
that entire cursed life!
The Navy, huh?
This is the third time this week.
Well, can you really blame them?
You're one of the most famous
pirates sailing the seas right now.
Captain Kuro is a superstar.
You're right.
My infamy is what draws them to us.
That's why I'm going to
give up being Captain Kuro.
Yeah, wouldn't that be nice!
Except, the marines won't stop their
pursuit until Captain Kuro is dead.
I am going to die.
It would seem that the tumultuous
life of a pirate just isn't for me.
You can't quit, sir!
You're the ship's captain.
You can be captain now.
I have finally grown weary of this life.
It's over.
I'm killing myself for all to see.
Sir! Captain Kuro! Captain! Captain!
How many vessels are there? One!
Just one this time!
What should we do, captain?
Should we man the cannons?
We can blast them to splinters!
Lower a small boat into the
water. What? A boat! Now!
Vice Captain Django, Captain Kuro
just... Yeah, I know. Yeah, I know.
It's too dangerous for him
to go there by himself.
Don't tell me he's turning himself in.
What?
The cannon fire stopped.
Prepare to board the ship.
But, shouldn't we...
I didn't ask for your opinion.
That's an order. Yes, sir.
Better get ready for a fight, boys.
So that's why you... On three!
The Marines.
They've been wiped out.
Now, then, let's begin this plan.
Come on, pull yourself together.
I was kind enough to let
you and you alone survive.
Just do it.
I'm not kneeling to you.
Finish me off and get it over with.
You'll be perfect.
If you can still howl this much with
a shattered jaw, you should do fine!
Today is the greatest day of your life.
Today is the day you
captured Captain Kuro.
You should be ever so grateful to me.
I'm giving you the head of Captain Kuro.
Your name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was your doing.
One.
Two.
Django.
My name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was my doing.
And you are the brave marine who
caught the infamous Captain Kuro.
Return to base and see
that he gets executed.
One.
Two.
Django.
I am the brave marine who caught
the infamous Captain Kuro?
You're doing it again, Vice Captain.
Perfect.
When my double gets executed,
Captain Kuro will disappear from the
Earth, and I will live the life I deserve.
And when my plan succeeds today,
after three years of planning,
revising, and waiting,
my goal will be achieved in its entirety.
Wealth and peace of mind
will finally be mine.
Do you understand now, boy?
I will not allow this perfect
plan years in the making to fail.
My plan will not be disrupted
by an urchin like you!
It would seem that you can do
a lot more than just stretch.
That's right.
I've been toughening
myself up to be a pirate
Know what don't want a reputation
Then don't be a pirate!
You're just greedy, Kuro.
But I have ambition!
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would leave me.
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever
changes, I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?